HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series II. Staff Photographs, 1940-2001
  - Subseries A. Staff, A-Z, circa 1940-circa 1994
    - Ann F. Zeitung (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 41)
    - David B. Zenoff (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 41)
    - Melanie Zibit, circa 1985 (Box 41)
    - Elden W. Ziegler (Research Assistant), Jr., circa 1960 (Box 41)
    - Ben-Ami Zucherman (Research Assistant), circa 1969 (Box 41)
  - Subseries B. Unidentified Individual Staff and Contact Sheets, 1940-1989
    - Unidentified woman, circa 1940 (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff, 1940s-1950s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff, 1960s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified woman, circa 1960 (Box 42)
    - Unidentified woman, circa 1965 (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff, 1970s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff, 1980s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff, 1987 (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff contact sheets, 1960s-1980s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff contact sheets, 1980s (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff contact sheets, circa 1985 (Box 42)
    - Unidentified staff contact sheets, 1989 (Box 42)
  - Subseries C. Departments, A-Z, circa 1922-1980s
    This series consists of group photographs of HBS administrative departments. The photographs show the functions of various offices and show departments at various HBS events. Included in this subseries are photographs of the Bureau of Business Research, the Written Analysis of Cases (WAC) graders, and the Audio-Visual department filming for case research.
    - Admissions, 1946 (Box 43)
    - Admissions, 1955 (Box 43)
    - Admissions, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Alumni Office (External Relations), 1950s (Box 43)
    - Alumni Office (External Relations), 19570s-1980s (Box 43)
    - Audio-Visual Department, 1950s (Box 43)
    - Audio-Visual Department- Filming Athena Electronics case study, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Audio-Visual Department, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Audio-Visual Department, circa 1980, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Baker Library, 1930s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library, 1940s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Circulation, 1940s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library, 1950s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library, 1960s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Circulation, 1960s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Manuscripts and Archives, 1963 (Box 43)
    - Baker Library, 1970s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Manuscripts and Archives, 1972-1974 (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Corporate Records, 1974 (Box 43)
    - Baker Library, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Manuscripts and Archives, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Business Information Analysts, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Baker Library- Staff album, 1950-1992 (Box 47)
      Staff album originally compiled by Lorna Daniells in 1985 with additional photographs added between 1985-1992. Contains photographs of Baker Library staff dating from 1950-1992 with annotations by Lorna Daniells. Photographs depict various staff events such as parties and trainings as well as staff at work.
    - Barber Shop, 1950s (Box 43)
    - Barber Shop, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Bureau of Business Research, circa 1922 (Box 43)
    - Bureau of Business Research, 1923 (Box 43)
      Includes photographs from the National Shoe Retailers Association annual meeting, 1923.
    - Case Services Center- Distribution of Cases, 1940s (Box 43)
    - Case Services Center- Distribution of Cases, 1950s (Box 43)
    - Case Services Center- Distribution of Cases, 1960s (Box 43)
    - Case Services Center, 1965 (Box 43)
    - Case Services Center, circa 1970 (Box 43)
    - Case Services Center- Distribution of Cases, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Computer Services, 1980s (Box 43)
    - Dining Halls, 1940s (Box 43)
    - Dining Halls, 1950s (Box 43)
    - Dining Halls, 1960s (Box 43)
    - Dining Halls, 1970s (Box 43)
    - Division of Research, 1949 (Box 44)
    - Division of Research, circa 1950 (Box 44)
    - Division of Research, circa 1955 (Box 44)
    - Division of Research- Editorial Services, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1950s-1980s (Box 44)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1966 (Box 44)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1979 (Box 44)
    - Harvard Business School Press, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Harvard Business School Press, circa 1980, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
    - Harvard Cooperative Society, 1950s-1980s (Box 44)
    - Morgan Hall offices, 1940s (Box 44)
    - Morgan Hall offices, 1950s (Box 44)
    - Morgan Hall offices, 1960s (Box 44)
    - Office of the Dean, 1958 (Box 44)
    - Operational Support Services, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Placement Office, 1940s-1950s (Box 44)
    - Placement Office, 1954-1978 (Box 44)
    - Placement Office, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Print Shop, 1963 (Box 44)
    - Research Assistants, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Registrars' Office, 1950s (Box 44)
    - Registrars' Office, 1980s (Box 44)
    - Written Analysis of Cases (WAC) Graders, 1940s-1950s (Box 44)
- Series III. HBS Fellows, A-Z, circa 1954-1994
  This series consists of photographs of individuals who have received fellowships at HBS. When known, the type of fellowship has been noted.
  - Jutta Allmendinger, circa 1991 (Box 45)
  - Hayward S. Anderson (Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1958 (Box 45)
  - Wayne E. Baker (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), 1990s (Box 45)
  - Brent D. Barnett (Research Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Kermit W. Bird (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Timothy F. Bresnahan (Marvin Bower Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Robert A. Burgelman (Marvin Bower Fellow), circa 1991 (Box 45)
  - David Carlson (Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1956 (Box 45)
  - Benzion Chanowitz (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Arthur S. Choo (Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1957 (Box 45)
  - Joanne B. Ciulla (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), 1990s (Box 45)
  - Welsley M. Cohen, Jr. (Research Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - George Constantinides (Marvin Bower Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Joseph E. Cooper (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Melvin R. Copen (DBA 1967; Research Fellow), circa 1967 (Box 45)
  - Saul Englebourg (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Earling A. Erikson (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Jeffrey Fear (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), 1993 (Box 45)
  - Kashai Ferdows (Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - Rowland G. Freeman (MBA 1953; Visiting Associate in Business Research), circa 1960 (Box 45)
  - Tony Allan Freyer (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), 1975 (Box 45)
  - Gary B. Friesen (MBA 1985; Associate Fellow), circa 1985 (Box 45)
  - Louis P. Galambos, III (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Bradley T. Gale (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - Joseph M. Gieco (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), 1980s (Box 45)
  - Lee Gilbert, circa 1990, (Contact sheets) (Box 45)
  - Jason E. Green (MBA 1994; Charles M. Williams Fellow), 1994 (Box 45)
  - Oliver D. Hart (Marvin Bower Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Kathleen J. Hartford (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), 1981 (Box 45)
  - Richard Frederick Hirsh (Research Fellow), 1990s (Box 45)
  - Robert B. Hance (MBA 1988; Associate Fellow), 1988 (Box 45)
  - Donald F. Heany (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - Michael Hofman (Research Fellow in Social Psychology of Management), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Katherine Diane Hughes (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Blake Ives (Marvin Bower Fellow), 1986 (Box 45)
  - Sirkka L. Jarvenpaa (Marvin Bower Fellow), 1990s (Box 45)
  - Reece V. Jenkins (Research Fellow), circa 1960 (Box 45)
  - Robert Jenrett, Jr. (Research Fellow), circa 1960 (Box 45)
  - Sudhir Kakar, circa 1980 (Box 45)
  - Arthur Karuna-Karan (MBA 1969; Research Fellow), circa 1969 (Box 45)
  - Mark Keil (MBA 1991), 1991 (Box 45)
  - Kelt Kindick (MBA 1980), circa 1980 (Box 45)
  - Elizabeth King (Research Fellow), 1992 (Box 45)
  - Maurice N. Klein (Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - John R. Klug (MBA 1972; Research Fellow), circa 1972 (Box 45)
  - Pieter Kuin (Honorary Research Fellow), circa 1985 (Box 45)
  - William H. Lazonick (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Richard Lefwich (Marvin Bower Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - D. Paul Leitch (Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Thomas R. Lloyd (Research Fellow), circa 1970 (Box 45)
  - Bruce R. Marion (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Charles C. McArthur (Research Fellow), circa 1980 (Box 45)
  - James H. Madison (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Colman M. Mockler, Jr. (MBA 1954; Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1954 (Box 45)
  - Thomas Moronian (Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - Patrick Moreton (Charles M. Williams Fellow), 1991 (Box 45)
  - Paul Morrison (Associate Fellow), circa 1985 (Box 45)
  - David C. Mowery (Research Fellow), circa 1990 (Box 45)
  - Edgar A. Pessemier (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1956 (Box 45)
  - Paul L. Poston (Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1957 (Box 45)
  - Coimbatore K. Prahalad (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - Linda Randall (Associate Fellow), 1988 (Box 45)
  - Andrew D. Regan (Charles M. Williams Fellow), circa 1988 (Box 45)
  - Leonard S. Reich (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), circa 1985 (Box 45)
  - Michael Reich (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), 1980s (Box 45)
  - Joan Eric Ricart (Research Fellow), circa 1992 (Box 45)
  - Donna J. Rilling (Harvard-Newcomen Fellow), 1994 (Box 45)
  - Michael Roberts (Associate Fellow), circa 1987 (Box 45)
  - Elaine P. Rothman (Post-Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1980 (Box 45)
  - Daniel Scherlis (Associate Fellow), 1986 (Box 45)
  - Ronald L. Schill (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - Sidney Schoeffler (Visiting Research Fellow), circa 1970 (Box 45)
  - John K. Smith (Business History Research Fellow), 1986 (Box 45)
  - Merritt Roe Smith (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1985 (Box 45)
  - James H. Solton (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1958 (Box 45)
  - Rosario J. Tosiello (Business History Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - John Y.D. Tse (MBA 1957; Doctoral Research Fellow), circa 1957 (Box 45)
  - Charalambos A. Vlachoutsicos, circa 1954 (Box 45)
  - Rowen C. Vogel (Research Fellow), circa 1965 (Box 45)
  - William O. Wagnon (Research Fellow), 1971 (Box 45)
  - Ying Y. Wang (Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
  - George R. White (Senior Research Fellow), circa 1960 (Box 45)
  - Charles R. Wolf (Research Fellow), circa 1960 (Box 45)
  - Wallace R. Wormley (Research Fellow), circa 1975 (Box 45)
- Series IV. Affiliated Individuals, A-Z, 1920s-circa 1985
  This series consists of photographs of individuals affiliated with HBS but who are not faculty, fellows, staff or alumni.
  - Winthrop W. Aldrich, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Elizabeth Altman, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Roberto Artavia, circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - Tim Athos, circa 1970 (Box 46)
  - Dr. Arlie Back- Portrait painting, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - George F. Baker, 1920s (Box 46)
  - John J. Balles, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - George B. Beitzel, 1985 (Box 46)
  - Harry Bernhard, circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - Charles Breed, 1987 (Box 46)
  - Keith R. Bridston, 1973 (Box 46)
  - John Burnett, circa 1970 (Box 46)
  - Edward E. Carlson, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Harward Clark, circa 1970 (Box 46)
  - George E. Cole, circa 1935 (Box 46)
  - John C. Coleman, circa 1955 (Box 46)
  - Robert Coles, circa 1985 (Box 46)
  - Thomas G. Collins, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Douglas Copeland, circa 1950, (Oversize box) (Box OS 2)
  - Norman Crockitt, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Gaetan Couture, circa 1960 (Box 46)
  - Lawelle David, circa 1960 (Box 46)
  - C. Douglas Dillon, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Robert S. Donaldson, circa 1965 (Box 46)
  - C.L. Drasher, circa 1960 (Box 46)
  - Peter Drucker, 1952 (Box 46)
  - Lincoln Filene, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Walter R. Fleischer, June 1957 (Box 46)
  - H.S. Foxwell- Portrait paintings (Box 46)
  - Martin R. Gainsbrugh, circa 1960 (Box 46)
  - William George, 1983 (Box 46)
  - Walter S. Gilford, 1944 (Box 46)
  - Carter Glass- Portrait painting (Box 46)
  - Albert Gregory, circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - Dan Hampton, 1970 (Box 46)
  - W. Averell Harriman, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Christian A. Herter, 1953 (Box 46)
  - [Unidentified] Hower, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - George M. Humphrey, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Herbert F. Johnson, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Francis Keppel, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - Meyer Kestenbaum- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955 (Box 46)
  - [Unidentified] Kresge, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - [Unidentified] Loughleed, circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - Franklin J. Lunding, circa 1960 (Box 46)
  - Rene McPherson, 1980 (Box 46)
  - Kathryn May [Neeld], circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - James F. Oates, 1964 (Box 46)
  - Don A. Orton, 1962 (Box 46)
  - Alfons E. Roesle, 1978 (Box 46)
  - Alexandra Self, 1977 (Box 46)
  - Naomi Seligman, circa 1980 (Box 46)
  - Dr. John D. Talbott, circa 1930 (Box 46)
  - Richard Towne, circa 1950 (Box 46)
  - William E. Williams, circa 1965 (Box 46)
  - Unidentified individual, circa 1940 (Box 46)